<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<!DOCTYPE properties SYSTEM "http://java.sun.com/dtd/properties.dtd">
<properties>
	<comment/>
	<entry key="term.of.use.main.head.label">
	General terms and conditions of this website
	</entry>
	<entry key="term.of.use.main.head.content.paragraph.first.label">	
	Following legal information and notice governs the use of the website {0} (hereinafter referred to as, "this website"). 
	The offered services are available for all Users(hereinafter referred to as, the user) that are interests for wicket components.
	</entry>
	<entry key="term.of.use.main.head.content.paragraph.second.label">
	With the registration on this website the user accepts the term of use of this website. The use of the services of this website requires a registration.
	By the registration process the user gets a username and a password that the user agrees to save securely. The user is responsible for the confidentiality from his password.
	</entry>
	<entry key="term.of.use.legal.references.head.label">
	1. Item of terms
	</entry>
	<entry key="term.of.use.legal.references.content.paragraph.first.label">
	This website provides wicket components. 
	The simple membership is free of costs. Services that are fee required are special tagged and are pointed out.
	The user commits to keep his data up to date.The user is responsible for the confidentiality from his password.
	</entry>
	<entry key="term.of.use.legal.references.content.paragraph.second.label">
	If the user is under-age than the user can register only with the consent of the parents. This website assumes that if a user is under-age he has the consent of the parents.
	The parents of the under-age user accepts the responsibility for every behavior of the under-age user on this website.
	The parents of the under-age user knows that this website can have content that are not appropriate for under-age users.
	</entry>
	<entry key="term.of.use.contract.head.label">
	2. Contract formation
	</entry>
	<entry key="term.of.use.contract.content.paragraph.first.label">
	A contract between the user and this website is concluded when the user has registered successfully to this website. 
	This website reserves the right, the data of the users to review, verify, validate or check in any shape or form.
	</entry>
	<entry key="term.of.use.data.protection.head.label">
	3. Data protection policy
	</entry>	
	<entry key="term.of.use.data.protection.head.content.paragraph.first.label">
	With the registration the user agrees that all personal data can be saved and edit in any way on this website. 
	The user agrees that all her or his profile data are visible for other users. Exceptional case is the email address and password. 
	Disclaimer: Despite careful control we assume no liability for the content of external links. For the content of linked pages their operators are responsible.
	</entry>	
	<entry key="term.of.use.copyright.head.label">
	4. Copyright
	</entry>
	<entry key="term.of.use.copyright.paragraph.first.label">
	All published content and works are copyrighted and is only for private use allowed.
	</entry>
	<entry key="term.of.use.cancellation.head.label">	
	5. Cancellation
	</entry>
	<entry key="term.of.use.cancellation.content.paragraph.first.label">
	The user is authorized, to unregister at any time(this means that all personal data will be lost).
	With the unregistration of the user from this website the contract between them is termed.
	</entry>
	<entry key="term.of.use.cancellation.content.paragraph.second.label">
	If the user owns a premium membership and unregister from this website 
	he renounces of all services for the rest of the time of the premium membership and renounces of payback payments.
	</entry>
	<entry key="term.of.use.cancellation.content.paragraph.third.label">
	This website is authorized to cancel a membership at any time, 
	if the user has made false statements to the registration process or made false statements to a later time. 
	In this case already payed fees are not payed back.
	</entry>
	<entry key="term.of.use.liability.head.label">
	6. Liability
	</entry>
	<entry key="term.of.use.liability.content.paragraph.first.label">
	This website is not liable for damages or losings of any kind that may be incurred due to a lack of precision, 
	up-to-dateness, completeness, detailedness or errors in the content of the informations from the users. 
	</entry>
	<entry key="term.of.use.liability.content.paragraph.second.label">
	This website has no obligation to check or monitoring the content of the information from the users. 
	</entry>
	<entry key="term.of.use.liability.content.paragraph.third.label">
	This website is not liable for any technical disturbances and does not guarantee the availability, 
	continuity or infallibility of this website operation.
	</entry>
	<entry key="term.of.use.liability.content.paragraph.fourth.label">
	This website is not liable for any damages or losses any kind, for actions on this website that are caused from a third party.
	This website is not liable for any damages or losses any kind, that are caused from any user on this website.
	</entry>
	<entry key="term.of.use.rights.and.duties.of.the.user.head.label">
	7. Rights and duties of the user
	</entry>
	<entry key="term.of.use.rights.and.duties.of.the.user.content.introduction.label">
	All the content of the informations,
		comments, opinions, advertisement and other content from users have to
		conform the truth. The content from the published offers have to
		comply with the legal requirements, consider the intellectual property
		laws and to comply the quality requirements and specifications from
		this website.	
	</entry>
	<entry key="term.of.use.rights.and.duties.of.the.user.content.to.satisfy.label">
	By published of any oppinions and other content and
		informations is to keep the followed restrictions:
	</entry>
	<entry key="term.of.use.rights.and.duties.of.the.user.content.paragraph.first.label">
	The content of the informations should not violate against the
		legislation of the host country.
	</entry>
	<entry key="term.of.use.rights.and.duties.of.the.user.content.paragraph.second.label">
	The content of the informations should not violate against the national
		or international law.
	</entry>
	<entry key="term.of.use.rights.and.duties.of.the.user.content.paragraph.third.label">
	The content of the informations should not damage the image, name and the
		good reputation of this website.
	</entry>
	<entry key="term.of.use.rights.and.duties.of.the.user.content.paragraph.fourth.label">
	The content of the informations should not contain any criminal content.
	</entry>
	<entry key="term.of.use.rights.and.duties.of.the.user.content.paragraph.fifth.label">
	The content of the informations should not contain any improperly,
		obscene, profanity, rudely or vile language.
	</entry>
	<entry key="term.of.use.rights.and.duties.of.the.user.content.paragraph.sixth.label">
	The content of the informations should not violate against the human
		rights.
	</entry>
	<entry key="term.of.use.rights.and.duties.of.the.user.content.paragraph.seventh.label">
	The content of the informations should not attack, references or making
		ridiculous any political or religious orientation.
	</entry>
	<entry key="term.of.use.rights.and.duties.of.the.user.content.paragraph.eighth.label">
	The content of the informations should not violate against the protection
		from minors.
	</entry>
	<entry key="term.of.use.rights.and.duties.of.the.user.content.paragraph.ninth.label">
	The content of the informations should not violate against the protection
		from human rights.
	</entry>
	<entry key="term.of.use.rights.and.duties.of.the.user.content.paragraph.tenth.label">
	The content of the informations should not violate against the protection
		from the sphere of personal privacy.
	</entry>
	<entry key="term.of.use.rights.and.duties.of.the.user.content.paragraph.eleventh.lable">
	The content of the informations should not violate against property
		rights, trade mark rights, copyright and related rights.
	</entry>
	<entry key="term.of.use.rights.and.duties.of.the.user.content.closure.paragraph.first.label">
	This website reserves the right, any content of the informations from
		users that does not conform the principles and directives of this
		website to let unpublished.
	</entry>
	<entry key="term.of.use.rights.and.duties.of.the.user.content.closure.paragraph.second.label">
	This website is not liable for any damages or losses any kind, that are caused from any user on this website.
	The user undertakes to indemnify and compensate this website by penalty, cost, tax or any other burden deriving 
	by not complying with the described rights and duties of the user above.
	</entry>
	<entry key="term.of.use.modifications.clause.head.label">
	8. alteration of the term of use
	</entry>
	<entry key="term.of.use.modifications.clause.content.paragraph.first.label">
	This website reserves the right, to alter this term of use or to author a new term of use.
	</entry>
	<entry key="term.of.use.modifications.clause.content.paragraph.second.label">
	The user agrees, with the altered or new term of use when there will be changed. The user will be informed with an email that the term of use are altered.
	The user have the opportunity to cancel or unregister from this website in a period of time(21 days) for complaints if he does not agree with the altered or new term of use.
	</entry>
	<entry key="term.of.use.modifications.clause.content.paragraph.third.label">
	The information about the altered or new term of use can and will be send to the given email address from the user.
	</entry>	
	<entry key="term.of.use.salvatorius.clause.head.label">
	9. Salvatorius clause
	</entry>
	<entry key="term.of.use.salvatorius.clause.content.paragraph.first.label">
	If one or more of this agreements in this contract is void of law, the rest of this contract will be still valid and active.
	</entry>
	<entry key="term.of.use.place.of.fulfilment.and.place.of.jurisdiction.and.other.regulations.head.label">
	10. Place of fulfilment and of jurisdiction and other regulations
	</entry>
	<entry key="term.of.use.place.of.fulfilment.and.place.of.jurisdiction.and.other.regulations.current.place.label">
	Stuttgart
	</entry>
	<entry key="term.of.use.place.of.fulfilment.and.place.of.jurisdiction.and.other.regulations.content.paragraph.firstlabel">
	Place of fulfilment and of jurisdiction is the city {0}. Every changes, subsidiary agreements, and complements requires the written form.
	</entry>
	<entry key="term.of.use.cookies.head.label">
	11. Cookies
	</entry>
	<entry key="term.of.use.cookies.content.paragraph.first.label">
	For our quality assurance and extend the functionality of our offer on the Internet, we use site cookies. 
	These are text files that are stored on the user's computer. 
	We track over the cookies the number of visits on our website. We use this information solely to improve our website.
	</entry>
</properties>
